

Total 3 years of Experienced with Core Java, Collections & Design Patterns Proficient in technologies such as Spring -MVC,SpringBoot, Hibernate, JPA, JavaScript/JQuery, Restful web API and MySQL.

Good in Data Structures



Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore Total Experience: 2 Year(s) 9 Month(s)

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Mangalore, Mysore Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming / Highest Degree: BE [Computer Science]

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: software engineer, software developer, software development, application programming, application

maintenance,requirement analysis,java,spring mvc,hibernate,spring boot,ajax,html,css,javascript,json,mysql,eclipse,Microservices

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 20-Jan-21 Last Modified: 20-Jan-21

Summary

3 years relevant Experience in Java Technology Core java, JavaScript and Hibernate, Spring(MVC). Experience on SpringBoot,MicroSevices ,RESTful Web Services And JUnit.

Good knowledge of Object Oriented Language Concept.

Used Tools like Tortoise svn, Git hub.

Exposure to Agile methodology.

Excellent in Design patterns like MVC (model view controller).

Work Experience

Unilog Content Solutions as Software Engineer -Java Sep 2019 to Jun 2020

Worked on the technologies are SpringBoot, Micro services and Java

ArisGlobal Software Ltd as Associate Software Engineer Sep 2017 to Sep 2019

Used a Techonogies are Spring mvc, Hibernate, Mysql java 1.8

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computer Science and Engineering) from Vishvesvaraya Technological University, Belgaum in 2016

PG: BE (Computer Science) in 0

Duration: Sep 2019 - May 2020 Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Team Size: 6

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience	
JAVA	1.8	2020	2 Year(s) 9 Month(s)	
MicroServices		2020	1 Year(s) 0 Month(s)	
Spring (MVC), Hibernate	latest	2020	2 Year(s) 6 Month(s)	
spring boot	4.0.0	2020	2 Year(s) 0 Month(s)	
AJAX, Html, javascript	5	2020	2 Year(s) 6 Month(s)	
JQuery and JSON.	3	2020	2 Year(s) 0 Month(s)	
Tomcat	8	2020	3 Year(s) 0 Month(s)	
Eclipse	oxygen	2020	3 Year(s) 0 Month(s)	
MySQL	latest	2020	2 Year(s) 0 Month(s)	
JQUERY	3	2020	2 Year(s) 0 Month(s)	

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Expert			
Kannada	Expert			

Projects

Project Title: E commerce Client: HMI and FG

Nature of Employment: Full Time

Project Location: mysore Role: Programmer

Skill Used: java hibernate spring mvc

Role Description: full stack

Project Details: ecommerce applications

Project Title: LSRIMS
Client: japan based client
Nature of Employment: Eul

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: Sep 2017 - Sep 2019
Onsite / Offsite:

Project Details: Project: #1

Project : LSRIMS Sept 2017 Sept 2019

Team 8

Environment Windows 10

Technology core java 1.8, Spring, Hibernate, Javascript, JUnit.

Tools Tortoise SVN, JIRA.

Server Tomcat 7.0

Description:

LifeSphere RIMS - Regulatory Information Management System. LifeSphere RIMS is a cloud-based regulatory information management solution (RIMS) that provides intuitive, mobile-enabled handling of all regulatory affairs processes by headquarters, regulatory operations, regional managers and local affiliates.

The regulatory planning module streamlines the management of activities and resources associated with global regulatory submissions by automating the definition, distribution and reporting of project plans globally and locally. As a result, LifeSphere RIMS improves visibility across the organization, providing a global view of issues while enabling faster, informed decision-making at a lower cost.

Responsibilities Programming /coding adhering to coding standards. Developing V

Affirmative Action

Category: OBC - non-creamy Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Countries: Australia, Japan, Canada

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time